

# MUKUL SAINI

WEB DEVELOPER
GRAPHIC DESIGNER

# CONTACT

- +91 8769506494
- khisismemukul@gmail.com
- in LinkenIn
- Github
- Bē Behance

# **SOFT SKILLS**

- Leadership/Team Player
- Problem Solving
- Quick Learner
- Attention to detail

### **LANGUAGES**

- English
- LiigiisiHindi

# **EDUCATION**

POORNIMA INSTITUTE OF ENGINEERING AND TECHNOLOGY, JAIPUR(RAJ)

Aug 2019 - Present | Pursuing B-tech in Computer Science Engineering.

SVM Public School

2018 - 2019 12th Standard | PCM

### ABOUT ME

Full-Stack Developer with 3+ years of experience leading both front-end with the ability to perform well in team/individual. Skilled in writing applications interface code via Javascript and ReactJS and React Native with MVC architecture. I build websites, mobile apps, and graphics that delight and inform.

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **E-CELL, IIT BOMBAY**

Web Coordinator · Internship Worked on a MERN Stack Project as a leader, with my team.

April 2021 - Sep 2021 · 6 mos

#### **CREATIVE GEEK STUDIO**

Front-End Developer Video Editor | Animator

Build frontend for different websites, using REACT and MUI. And made animated videos using After Effects.

Jan 2021- Mar 2021

#### **DIGIVENTRY MARKETING**

Graphic & Motion Designer
I created logos, posters, video edit,
graphic works with Adobe softwares.
April 2021 - Jun 2021 · 3 mos

#### THE WEBCONIX

Graphic & Motion Designer I created posters, video edit, and other graphic works.

Aug 2020 - April 2021

### **PROJECTS**

#### **T-Shirt Hub**

- A MERN Stack e-commerce Project.
- With a stripe and brain-tree payment gateway
- MVC architecture Based.

#### **REACT-NATIVE FOOD APP**

- Made with custom API.
- User can add food to cart, search food and restaurants.

#### **SOVA SKILLS**

 Worked as a nodejs developer on this freelance project.

#### **COVID RESOURCES WEB APP**

 This web app provides and donates medical supplies.

#### **RENTWEB E-COMMERCE**

 This is an online product renting website made with PHP/MySQL.

### NODE MOVIE SEARCH API WEB APP

- Users can Search Lists of Movies and Series based on keywords.
- Made with OMDB API with Node and Express.

## **TECH SKILLS**

- Front-end Development: ReactJS, MUI, JavaScript
- Back-end Development: JavaScript, Nodejs, Express
- Mobile App Development: React-Native
- Databases: MongoDB,MySQL
- Graphic Designing: Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop
- UI/UX Design: Adobe XD, Figma
- Video Editing: Adobe After Effects, Media Encoder
- Language: C, C++,Java
- Operating System: Linux, Windows, Mac
- Git & GitHub